(Leonard:)That's actually good.
Why didn't I think of that?
(Sheldon:)Some people are otters,
some people are rocks.
(Leonard:)I wonder if there's a way
we could give the idea a trial run.
(Howard:)I could call my old middle school, see if
we can talk to some of the female students.
(Leonard:)Great. Try to set up something
for us to go over there.
(Sheldon:)Hold on. While I'm comfortable
speaking about science...
(Sheldon:)...I'm not sure I know how to spark the
interest of school children. Better Google it.
(Howard:)What exactly are you looking up?
"How do I get 12-year-old girls excited?"
- No!
(Raj:)Thanks again for letting me crash
girl's night.
(Penny:)Are you kidding?
You brought fancy wine and made fondue.
(Penny:)I've slept with guys for less.
It's ajoke.